var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٌ",
        "answer": "the One",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "rootWordId": 20,
        "tlit": "aḥadun",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " قُلْ هُوَ اللَّهُ أَحَدٌ",
        "rootWord": "أ ح د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَحَد",
        "waznEnglish": "one, anyone",
        "waznTlit": "aḥad",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٌ",
        "answer": "any [one]",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "rootWordId": 20,
        "tlit": "aḥadun",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَمْ يَكُنْ لَهُ كُفُوًا أَحَدٌ",
        "rootWord": "أ ح د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَحَد",
        "waznEnglish": "one, anyone",
        "waznTlit": "aḥad",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2844",
        "rootWordId": 61,
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " قُلْ هُوَ اللَّهُ أَحَدٌ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱللَّه",
        "waznEnglish": "Allah",
        "waznTlit": "allah",
        "waznType": "Proper noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2845",
        "rootWordId": 61,
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " اللَّهُ الصَّمَدُ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱللَّه",
        "waznEnglish": "Allah",
        "waznTlit": "allah",
        "waznType": "Proper noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّمَدُ",
        "answer": "the Eternal, the Absolute",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 860,
        "tlit": "l-ṣamadu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " اللَّهُ الصَّمَدُ",
        "rootWord": "ص م د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ص م د",
        "waznEnglish": "the Eternal, the Absolute",
        "waznTlit": "ṣād mīm dāl",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1615",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " قُلْ هُوَ اللَّهُ أَحَدٌ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَالَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to say",
        "waznTlit": "qāla",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُفُوًا",
        "answer": "equivalent",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1278,
        "tlit": "kufuwan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَمْ يَكُنْ لَهُ كُفُوًا أَحَدٌ",
        "rootWord": "ك ف أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك ف أ",
        "waznEnglish": "equivalent",
        "waznTlit": "kāf fā hamza",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "1357",
        "rootWordId": 1305,
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَمْ يَكُنْ لَهُ كُفُوًا أَحَدٌ",
        "rootWord": "ك و ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَانَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be",
        "waznTlit": "kāna",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلِدْ",
        "answer": "He begets",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "rootWordId": 1647,
        "tlit": "yalid",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " لَمْ يَلِدْ وَلَمْ يُولَدْ",
        "rootWord": "و ل د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَلَدَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to beget, to be born",
        "waznTlit": "walada",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُولَدْ",
        "answer": "He is begotten",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "rootWordId": 1647,
        "tlit": "yūlad",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surahnum": "112",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " لَمْ يَلِدْ وَلَمْ يُولَدْ",
        "rootWord": "و ل د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَلَدَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to beget, to be born",
        "waznTlit": "walada",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    }
]; 
export default words;